SINNI SINGLA

Contact

City:

Hyderabad, India

Phone:

+91 9872666643

Email:

sinnisingla@outlook.com

Website:

singla-s.github.io/myportfolio

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/sinnisingla

GitHub:

github.com/singla-s

Summary

Experienced full stack developer with 3+ years in the industry and high level proficiency in HTML, CSS, Angular, React Js, JQuery, expertise with C#, Node JS and more. Developed web applications across multiple APIs and third-party integrations.

Skill Highlights

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- C#, Node Js
- Rest API, JSON, XML
- Angular, React Js, JQuery
- Bootstrap
- SVN, GIT

Experience

Tata Consultancy Services, Hyderabad

Full Stack Developer - 10/2018 - currently working

- Design and Develop an incident dashboard for client using Angular, HTML, CSS and .Net Core Framework.
- Develop a feature to show the incidents globally by plotting the point of origin on a world map.
- Design multiple visualizations to show different statistics using Restful API, Google visualization and Highcharts.
- Implement SSO (Single Sign On) authentication with Salesforce as IDP.
- Design and Develop the Control Management System using HTML, CSS, JQuery, C# and .Net Framework.
- Migrate OAM Authentication to Azure AD Authentication while coordinating with the vendor.
- Work independently on multiple other applications to fulfill new feature requests from client.

Front End Developer - 02/2017 - 09/2018

- Design and Develop an application tracking website for client to track the applications based on information e.g. Technology Used, Infrastructure, Location of Deployment, Application Owner etc.
- Implement multiple grids with the capability of filtering, sorting, editing etc, along with export, import functionality.
- Develop visualizations using Jquery and Highcharts library.

Education

Bachelor of Engineering: **Computer Engineering** (2012-2016) **Thapar Institute of Engineering and Technology** *CGPA* – *8.46*